CONTACT

(407) 406-2557 amador.jessica98@gmail.com

Jessica Amador

Processing clerk | Educator

EDUCATION

Florida State University Bachelor of Science:

Secondary English Education

GPA: 3.76

Master of Science:

Curriculum and Instruction

GPA: 4.0

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent

Spanish - Fluent

SUMMARY

I am a former educator with experience in developing, designing, and presenting curriculum materials. I have been recognized for my communication and collaboration with others. I'm passionate about learning new things by taking on new challenges; I am currently working on a UX/UI course with an expected graduation in October 2024.

SKILLS

- Creating engaging presentations and educational material using Canva, Microsoft Office, Google Workspace, Figma, and Procreate
- Researching and applying educational and social methodologies to classrooms and workspaces.
- Utilizing UX/UI to design app screens on Figma and AdobeXD

EXPERIENCE

Processing Clerk — Costco

OCTOBER 2023 - PRESENT

- Consistently achieved metrics measurably better than expected averages.
- Obtained performance positive reviews from supervisors and customers.
- Demonstrated proficient abilities with company web pages and software
- Engaged competently and professionally with customers on phone calls to provide optimal outcomes

ESL Teacher — Harvest English Institute

JANUARY 2022 - JULY 2023

- Improved student outcomes by a measurable minimum of five percentage points
- Increased coworker collaboration by sharing self-prepared lesson materials such as worksheets and presentations
- Led engaging lessons for student groups sizes ranging from three to twenty-five students

ELA/ESL TEACHER, — Innovation Middle School

AUGUST 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

- Collaborated with a professional development team to create and modify standards-driven curriculum materials
- Provided engaging instruction to large student groups using research-driven methods and collaboratively created materials
- Attended and hosted meetings with guardians and professional development teams to provide essential accommodations for students